One of the things that we have been commenting on the most about everything that revolves around the Didi
una de las cosas que más hemos estado comentando sobre todo lo que gira en torno al caso de Didi
Camps case is their relationship and possible something that would have happened with Justin Bieber. Strange is the video in which
camps es su relación y posible eh algo que Hubiese pasado con Justin Bieber raro es el vídeo en el
we have not mentioned Justin Bieber Because almost everyone every day we get some news in
que no hemos mencionado a Justin Bieber Porque casi todos los días nos sale Alguna novedad de
fact in the last few hours Sources close to Justin have confirmed to a media outlet
hecho en las últimas horas Fuentes cercanas a Justin habrían confirmado a un medio de
that Justin is quite affected right now with everything that is happening, it is not
comunicación que Justin se encuentra ahora mismo bastante afectado con todo lo que está pasando no
exactly known very well what they wanted to give to understand with this topic when saying
se sabe exactamente muy bien Qué es lo que han querido dar a entender con este tema al decir
this but probably that many things are being removed from his past or that he is simply
esto pero probablemente que se estén removiendo muchas cosas de su pasado o que simplemente lo
having a hard time knowing that Didi is in jail for all the good relationship and the Rose
esté pasando mal sabiendo que Didi esté en la cárcel por toda la buena relación y el Rose
that he has had with him and that simply well According to this source, a media called Us Weekly does not like it,
que haya tenido con él y que simplemente pues no le guste según esta fuente a un medio llamado Us
the story that Justin experienced with Didi was quite harsh but all the processing
weekly la historia que vivió Justin con Didi fue bastante dura pero todo el procesamiento
and all the charges that are being brought against him because he is not finishing processing them well. In fact,
y todos los cargos que le están imputando pues no los está terminando de procesar bien De hecho
in the previous video I was with you showing a photograph that Justin's wife uploaded with
en el vídeo anterior os estuve enseñando una fotografía que subió la mujer de Justin con
which she sent a fairly direct message. Although they were direct, Justin is in a
la que lanzaba un mensaje bastante directo Aunque fueron en directa Justin está en una
difficult mental situation at the moment, he has a very difficult history with Didi and the accusations
situación mental difícil en estos momentos tiene una historia muy dura con Didi y las acusaciones
against him have been difficult to process. I also understand this as when you find out
en su contra han sido difíciles de procesar yo esto también lo entiendo como que al enterarte
more things that a person with whom you have had a close relationship has done that perhaps you did not
de más cosas que ha hecho una persona con las que has tenido relación cercana que a lo mejor tú no
know. Well, all this impacts you and if you already had a little doubt about that person, then you will fall
sabías Pues todo esto te impacta y esa persona si ya la tenías un poco en duda pues se te caiga
much more and will disappoint you much more by following the advice of his lawyers and also his
mucho más y te decepcione mucho más siguiendo los consejos de sus abogados y también de sus
advisors, he has remained as removed from the case and from all the media hype as possible, the
asesores se ha mantenido Lo más retirado del caso y de todo el revuelo mediático posible el
youtuber of the review has uploaded a couple of videos denying some of the conspiracies that There is
youtuber de la review ha subido un par de vídeos desmintiendo algunas de las conspiraciones que hay
around this topic, I recommend that you see it because it is another quite interesting point of view.
alrededor de este tema yo recomiendo que lo veáis porque es otro punto de vista bastante interesante
By the way, and it is very good. And I especially highlight a compilation of evidence that he would have shown
Por cierto y está muy bien Y en especial destaco una recopilación de pruebas que habría mostrado
in his video, which denies the fact that Justin had passed 48 hours under Didi's tutelage
en su vídeo la que se desmiente el hecho de que Justin hubiera pasado 48 horas bajo la tutela de
. In other words, if the two of them had been alone and spent 48 hours together, this would not
Didi O sea que hubieran estado los dos a solas pasado 48 horas juntos esto no demostraría que
magically prove that Didi has abused Justin. The only thing that could prove that would be if Justin said
Didi ha abusado de Justin mágicamente lo único que podría demostrar eso sería si Justin deía
yes and said yes, Didi abused me, but that didn't even happen. has happened nor does it look like it will happen
adante y decir sí Didi abusó de mí pero eso ni ha ocurrido ni tiene pinta de que vaya a suceder
considering that they were still friends Until last year and we can publicly see all the
teniendo en cuenta que seguían siendo amigos Hasta el año pasado y podemos ver públicamente todas las
things he did from the October 26th when he arrived until he left October 26th Justin bber and
cosas que hizo desde el 26 de octubre que llegó hasta que se fue 26 de octubre Justin bber y
Los Angeles the October 27 he had a photo shoot October 27 he was on a
Los Ángeles el 27 de octubre se hizo una sesión de fotos 27 de octubre estuvo en una cancha de
basketball court on October 28 he went to a radio interview on October 29 he went to a
baloncesto el 28 de octubre fue a una entrevista una radio el 29 de octubre fue a un evento de
Microsoft event as you can see here on October 30 there are no photos but Yes, we have a tweet from Justin
Microsoft como podéis ver aquí del 30 de octubre no hay fotos pero sí tenemos tweet de Justin
Bieber. On October 31, he was at another radio station giving another interview in October wearing the
Bieber el 31 de octubre estuvo en otra estación de radio dando otra entrevista de octubre llevando la
same jacket and the radio station was there from 6 pm to 8 pm and the video he recorded with
misma chaqueta y la estación de radio estuvo desde las 6 pm hasta las 8 pm y el vídeo que grabo con
Didi It's daytime now starting at 800 pm it is already night and on top of that the radio station
Didi Es de día y a partir de las 800 pm ya está siendo de noche y encima la estación de radio
attended a Halloween party with his friends here you can see him with his friends it is already night
asistió a una fiesta de Halloween con sus amigos aquí le podéis ver con sus amigos ya es de noche
And this is the complete timeline at an event in Levis then in Didi's house and then at
Y esta es la línea tiempo completa en un evento en Levis luego en la casa de Didi y luego por la
night he went to the radio and a party with his friends. In addition, he would also comment on the question that until
noche fue a la radio y una fiesta con sus amigos además también comentaría la cuestión de que hasta
last year both Didi and Justin maintained at least cordiality or that they were friends Until
el año pasado tanto Didi como Justin mantenía por lo menos una cordialidad o que eran amigos Hasta
last year and that Justin didn't need Didi to have fallen for all the additions
el año pasado y que a Justin no le hacía falta de Didi para haber caído en todas las adiciones
he fell into, let's not even say he spent 48 hours with Didi, this is a filthy lie, but
en las que cayó vamos que ni de coña se pasó 48 horas con Didi esto es una mentira cochina pero
even if I have spent 48 hours with him, which is not the case, let's remember that bber was always accompanied
Incluso si he pasado 48 horas con él que no es así recordemos que hace bber siempre iba acompañado a
everywhere with his mother, the only time when Justin Bieber let himself talk to his mother was
todos sitios con su madre la única época donde se dejó hablar Justin Bieber con su madre fue
when he got into lasd eem gas and that was already in 2015 when he was already more than of age, there are
cuando él se metió en lasd eem gas y eso ya fue en 2015 cuando él ya era más que mayor de edad hay
people saying that Justin bber got into those substances because of Didi when the truth is
gente diciendo que Justin bber se metió en esas sustancias por culpa de Didi cuando lo cierto Es
that you don't need a guy to get you into those kinds of substances for you to get fully involved and be
que no hace falta que te meta un tío en esa clase de sustancias para que tú te metas de lleno y seas
a drug addict Yes and without bber he was abused by Didi There is no proof of this
un drog e gem adicto Sí y sin bber fue abusado por Didi No hay ninguna prueba al respecto de
Not even the slightest bit of it, but literally not even a little bit of evidence and now like this people
ello ni la más mínima pero es que literalmente ni un poquito de evidencia y ahora así la gente
put it everywhere saying oh how bad how Justin was abused on this channel we have commented
lo pone por todos lados diciendo ay qué mal Cómo fue abusado a Justin en este canal hemos comentado
as you already know all the conspiracy theories the rumors trying to differentiate it or At least
como ya sabéis todas las teorías conspirativas los rumores intentando diferenciarlo o por lo menos
making it clear what the real and verified data are in fact. Thanks also to all the
dejándolo claro de lo que son los datos reales y comprobados de hecho Gracias también a todos los
rumors and all the theories that have been put forward and that we have been commenting on, we have had 16 videos that,
rumor y a todas las teorías que se han ido sacando y hemos ido comentando hemos tenido 16 vídeos que
by the way, I recommend that you go through the list of complete reproduction and see it all
por cierto os recomiendo que os paséis por la lista de reproducción completa y lo veáis todo
if you want to be well immersed in the whole topic of the case of Cindy the camps if we had not
si queréis estar bien empapados sobre todo el tema este del caso de Cindy the camps si no hubiéramos
also commented on all the conspiracy theories that have come out we would have been left with three
comentado también todas las teorías conspirativas que han salido nos hubiéramos quedado en tres
videos and I think you don't believe that so what pass my youth welcome one more day to the Channel I'm
vídeos y creo que no creéis eso así que qué pasa mi chavalería bienvenidos un día más al Canal soy
oliveira if you've come here from a rebound and you didn't know me I invite you to subscribe to the Channel
oliveira si has llegado aquí de rebot y no me conocías te invito a que te suscribas al Canal
you already know that here we are commenting on all the viral salse itos from the internet and
ya sabéis que aquí vamos comentando todos los salse itos virales de internet y de la
television So if you you are interested And you like this type of content I force you to subscribe
televisión Así que si te interesa Y te gusta este tipo de contenido te obligo a que te suscribas
it is mandatory press the subscribe button and you will not miss anything I upload well in the
vale obligatorio pulsa al botón de suscribirte y no te perderás nada de lo que subo bueno en los
last few days Didi has been declaring we do not have images we do not have audio they have not let the
últimos días ha estado Didi declarando no tenemos imágenes no tenemos audio no han dejado pasar las
camera or any digital recording method, the only thing that some accredited media outlets have stopped passing by,
cámara ni ningún método digital de grabación lo único que han dejado de pasar algunos medios de
some journalists with lifelong paper and pencil to take notes.
comunicación acreditados algunos periodistas con papel y lápiz de toda la vida para tomar notas
So I will tell you everything that is known about that statement And how things are going to happen. Sometimes the rumors
Así que os comentaré todo lo que se sabe sobre esa declaración Y cómo va la cosa a veces los rumores
come from close sources, sometimes for example, like the case that I am going to give you below,
vienen de fuentes cercanas a veces por ejemplo como el caso que os voy a poner a continuación
Tupac's brother was commenting that he asked Didi at the time if he had anything
el hermano de Tupac estuvo comentando que le preguntó a Didi en su momento por si tenía algo
to do with the murder of his brother Tupac, who already I know that on that topic Well, there are a lot of
que ver en el asesinato de su hermano Tupac que ya sabé que sobre ese tema Pues hay un montón de
accusations and after 27 years the very brother of your pack affirms that he does not believe
señalamientos y después de 27 años el mismísimo hermano de tu pack afirma que él no se cree a
Didi And he does think perfectly well that he could have had something to do with his brother's death,
Didi Y sí que piensa perfectamente que pudo haber tenido algo que ver con la muerte de su hermano
you know. For example, Will's wife, who was a very good friend of Tupac, also thinks that Didi
ya sabéis que por ejemplo la mujer de Will sm smi que era muy amiga de Tupac también piensa que Didi
could have had something to do with it. There are many people who think that he is a very powerful person
podría haber tenido algo que ver son mucha gente lo que lo piensan que es una persona muy poderosa
with the ability to get out of Rosita on many occasions. accusations and some
con la capacidad de salir de Rosita en muchas ocasiones de algunas acusaciones y de algunos
acts my brother was King of the Hill top dog King of rap and with it comes a lot of jealousy
actos my brother was King of the Hill top dog King of rap and with it comes a lot of jealousy
I It's Pretty Direct there from 50 Cent Yes It was you know And I Know that everyone believes
I It's Pretty Direct there from 50 Cent Yes It was you know And I Know that everyone believes
that didy was involved in both these shootings that is what the streets have said for 27 years
that didy was involved in both these shootings that is what the streets have said for 27 years
We were all familiar with All the rumors and Stuff I said yeah Let me talk to him What did
We all were familiar with All the rumors and Stuff I said yeah Let me talk to him What did
he Say that day when he called you you know I have my guys With Me live guys and Uh we heard
he Say that day when he called you you know I have my guys With Me live guys and Uh we heard
What he Had to say basically said he ain't have Nothing to do with my brother's murder
What he Had to say basically said he ain't have Nothing to do with my brother's murder
Don't talk about things that are thinky posses of Looking that here we are7 28 years later
Don't talk about things that are thinky poss of Looking that here we are7 28 years later
the involvement him is quite High on the list our family you know we Still all wrapped up he
the involvement him is quite High on the list our family you know we Still all wrapped up he
was Still shaking The Bed he really Wanted to Tell Me Something I'm assuming It was something
was Still shaking The Bed he really Wanted to Tell Me Something I'm assuming It was something
Had to do with the hit I get the feeling quite strongly that you don't seem gotch of Something that all the journalists who have been in the room and have been able to see
Had to do with the hit I get the feeling quite strongly that you don't seems gotch of
Didi in person have highlighted
algo que han resaltado todos los periodistas que han estado en sala y han podido ver en
has been about his physical appearance. The journalists who have been able to see in person how
persona a Didi ha sido sobre su aspecto físico los periodistas que han podido ver en persona como se
Didi is currently and how he appeared in the room on the side of the player with a
encuentra actualmente Didi Y cómo apareció por la sala por un lateral del jugado con un traje
brown suit, the typical one from when you are in prison, I understand from there and that Didi would have recovered
marrón el típico de cuando estás en la cárcel entiendo de allí y es que Didi habría recuperado
now that he is not partying and sticking to excess the figure of the 90s, that is, he has seemed much
ahora que no está de fiestas y pegándose excesos la figura de los años 90 o sea ha parecido mucho
thinner and as I have already told you, well It has not been possible to take photographs or recordings and what
más delgado y como ya os he dicho pues no se han podido hacer fotografías ni grabaciones y lo que
we do have are drawings drawings that more or less represent the moments that have been lived in the
sí tenemos son dibujos dibujos que representan más o menos los momentos que se han vivido en
room. It seems that Didi could have been close to her children or almost all of her children and her mother as well.
sala al parecer Didi pudo estar cerca de sus hijos o de casi todos sus hijos y de su madre también de
his lawyers and gave them all a hug, he was seen laughing at several moments in the statement. The
sus abogados y les dio un abrazo a todos se le vio riéndose en varios momentos de la declaración la
prosecutor Emily Johnson has rejected the request of Didi's defense, which, as I already told you in the video
fiscal Emily Johnson ha rechazado la petición de la defensa de Didi que como ya os dije en el vídeo
Previously, I wanted to argue that it would be necessary to rule out the procedure to invalidate that video that
anterior quería alegar que habría que descartar del procedimiento invalidar ese vídeo que que
went so viral a few months ago where Didi in a hotel running through the corridors after
se viralizó tanto hace unos cuantos de meses donde Didi en un hotel corriendo por los pasillos detrás
that ex-partner literally beat up almost where it was demonstrated What was the attitude
de esa expareja le pegaba una paliza literalmente a casi donde se demostraba Cuál era la actitud
of Didi in privacy, well, not so intimate because we are talking about a hallway in a
de Didi en la intimidad bueno no tan íntima porque estamos hablando de un pasillo de un
fairly popular hotel and this would demonstrate that many things that have been said about him are
hotel bastante popular y esto demostraría Pues que muchas cosas que se han dicho sobre él pues son
true. The prosecutor has rejected the accusation that Didi's defense was making that That video
verdad la fiscal ha rechazado la acusación que la defensa de Didi estaba haciendo de que ese vídeo
was leaked by the government, well anyway, I'm not telling you either. In other words, the fact that
fue filtrado por parte del gobierno bueno en fin tampoco también os digo O sea a mí el hecho de que
they want to invalidate that video for the procedure seems silly to me because it would be as simple
quieran invalidar ese vídeo para al procedimiento me parece una tontería porque sería tan sencillo
as it is good, we discard the video but we have all the means of communication that have spoken
como bueno venga descartamos el vídeo pero tenemos todos los medios de comunicación que han hablado
on this topic, that is, in the end, the case of Almost is already prescribed. Furthermore, she reached
sobre este tema o sea al final el caso de Casi ya está prescrito Además ella llegó a
an agreement with him, that is, that is closed to him and they are not going to condemn him for what he did, they are not
un acuerdo con él o sea eso está cerrads himo y no lo van a condenar por eso que hizo no lo
going to ever condemn him for That beating, that video would only serve to give a little context
van a condenar ya nunca por esa paliza ese vídeo solamente serviría para dar un poco de contexto
and validity, not to the attitude and accusations that are being made to Didi. In the end,
y de validez no a la actitud y la acusaciones que se le están haciendo a Didi al final ya
I'll tell you, it doesn't matter to me if you present the video as such or a lot of media. digital communications
te digo lo mismo me da que presentes el vídeo como tal o un montón de medios de comunicación
on paper on TV that have echoed what appears in that video and the truth.
digitales en papel en tele que se han hecho Eco De lo que aparece dentro de ese vídeo y la verdad
So in the end, as such, I don't understand why they are so interested in canceling that video,
O sea que al final como tal tampoco entiendo yo Por qué tienen tanto interés en anular ese vídeo
that video has already been seen by the entire planet. In addition, the prosecutor says that she has more than 96
ese vídeo ya lo ha visto todo el planeta además la fiscal habla de que tiene más de 96 dispositivos
electronic devices. I imagine that they will be CDs and USBs. Also, this is the result of the raids
electrónicos yo me imagino que serán CDs eh USB también que esto es fruto de los allanamientos
that have been carried out both in Didi's mansions and in the private jet with 90 TB of
que han hecho tanto en las mansiones de Didi como en el Jet privado con atentos 90 tb de información
digital information. I mean, 90 tb doesn't just take up photographs, eh, not even
digital o sea 90 tb no lo los ocupa simplemente con fotografías eh Ni siquiera grabaciones de
audio recordings, I mean, there have to be quite powerful videos because the prosecutor talks about It's good that
audio o sea Ahí tiene que haber vídeos bastante potentes pues la fiscal habla de Que bueno que
why fight so much, not to reject that video in which she mistreats almost when they have In those
para qué tanta pelea no con rechazar ese vídeo en el que maltrata a casi cuando tienen en esos
90 TB, the evidence is much worse, that is, much worse. Who knows what is there recorded
90 tb pruebas muchísimo peores o sea muchísimo peores vete tú a saber lo que hay ahí grabado
in videos? I am completely sure that those are videos. 90 TB is like approximately 10,000
en vídeos estoy completamente seguro de que esos son vídeos 90 tb son como aproximadamente 10000
Blu-rays in 4K or more than 6,000 movies in 1080, that is. Full HD By the way, the prosecutor has commented
blu-rays en 4k o más de 6000 películas en 1080 o sea Full HD Por cierto la fiscal ha comentado
about these devices that there are some videos that are not capable of playing, I imagine that
sobre estos dispositivos que hay algunos vídeos que no son capaces de Reproducir me imagino que
due to the issues of formats, compatibility, drivers or whatever. But well, I imagine
por los temas de los formatos la compatibilidad los drivers o lo que sea Pero bueno Me imagino
that it will not be a problem that the FBI be able to solve in the end you can get all the
que no será un problema que el FBI sea capaz de solucionar al final puedes alcanzar toda la
possible documentation for when the trial is next year, this one you are seeing on
documentación posible para cuando sea el juicio para el año que viene este que estáis viendo en
the screen is the judge in charge of the Didi case arun suramin is the first judge of Indian origin
pantalla es el juez encargado del caso de Didi arun suramin es el primer juez de origen indio
in the district of New York was recently promoted by Joe Biden And apparently he has
en el distrito de Nueva York fue recientemente ascendido por Joe biden Y al parecer pues tien
a lot of experience in criminal and commercial cases, apparently the guy is a crack And
muchísima experiencia en Casos penales también mercantiles por lo visto el tío es un crack Y
well, Didi has seemed calm even sometimes when they were reminding him of the
bueno pues a Didi se le ha visto tranquilo incluso algunas veces cuando le estaban recordando los
charges that are being brought against him requesting, the guy was laughing, in fact, apparently they have charged him with more charges
cargos que se le están solicitando el tío se reía de hecho por lo visto le han imputado más cargos
than we already knew. Likewise, Didi had some smile there, that is, as if demonstrating
de los que ya sabíamos Igualmente Didi esaba alguna sonrisa por ahí o sea como demostrando
or at least interpreting an attitude that he would not be worried about everything that is
o por lo menos interpretando una actitud de que no estaría preocupado por todo lo que se
coming to him. Or maybe it will come to him and his lawyer, for his part, continues fighting and says that he will
le viene o puede que se le venga y su abogado por su parte pues sigue peleando y dice que va
do everything possible so that he is free until the trial date is in May of next year
a serc todo lo posible porque salga Libre hasta que sea la fecha del juicio en mayo del año que
decision to the circ and we to Keep trying to Get him out That's available to Us
viene decision to the circ and we to Keep trying to Get him out That's available to Us
I only know what happens and that hasn't happen What argument to exude hotel most
I only know what what happen and that hasn't happen What argument to exude hotel most
respectful put Our paper Yesterday and Notice that in fact what the lawyer has highlighted is
respectful put Our paped Yesterday and Fíjate que de hecho lo que ha destacado el abogado es
that the most difficult thing for Didi has been The issue of food, although it is not bad at all considering
que lo más difícil para Didi ha sido el tema de la comida que aunque no está nada mal teniendo en
that he is in a prison, is what the Metropolitan detention center
cuenta que está en una cárcel pues es lo que peor estaría llevando el centro de detención
where Coms is currently detained in would be the worst. It usually serves hamburgers, baked fish
Metropolitano donde coms se encuentra actualmente detenido normalmente sirve hamburguesas pescado
or meat tacos for lunch. during the week with scrambled eggs and
al horno o tacos de carne para el almuerzo durante la semana con huevos revueltos y
biscuits on the weekends for dinner they offer chicken fajitas pasta and roast beef as well as
galletas los fines de semana para la cena ofrecen fajitas de pollo pasta y roast beef además de
healthy and vegetarian meals And well, as I was telling you a few minutes ago,
comidas saludables y vegetarianas Y bueno pues como os estaba comentando hace unos minutos
her children, well, almost all of her children, her mother as well, whom you can also see in the
sus hijos bueno casi todos sus hijos su madre también a la que también podéis ver en los
drawings that have been drawn of her, you can also see her in the background with glasses, they attended the
dibujos que la han dibujado también la podéis ver por ahí de fondo con gafa asistieron a la
Didi's statement to see him in person, not to have that contact, no And to
declaración de Didi para verlo en persona no para tener ese contacto no Y para demostrarle
also show him support as they are there, the mother was booed a few times at the exit
también apoyo como que están ahí la madre fue abucheada unas cuantas de veces a la salida
and entrance of the courthouse with people yelling at her, your son is a predator
y a la entrada de los juzgados con gente que le gritaba tu hijo es un depredador
. before you go back to
your before you go back to
JC and Billon's lawyer, he is a fairly well-known lawyer for those of us who follow
el abogado de JC y billon es un abogado bastante conocido para los que seguimos
celebrity cases Alex Spiro Alex Spiro already represented Alex Balvin in his case, it is a case
caso de celebridades Alex espiro Alex Spiro ya representó a Alex Balvin en su caso es un caso
that we have also followed on the channel here you have the video I recommend that you see it, it turned out
que hemos seguido también en el canal por ahí tenéis el vídeo recomiendo que lo veáis salió
quite well for Alex after firing a gun that was supposed to be a prop
bastante bien para Alex luego de disparar un arma que se supone que era de utilería
and killing a producer, you have the context in the video, okay, he came out innocent and
y matar a una productora por ahí tenéis el contexto en el vídeo vale salió inocente y
is currently also the lawyer for the mayor of New York who is right now accused of
actualmente también es el abogado del alcalde de Nueva York que está ahora mismo acusado de
corruption and that he has a certain good deal with Didi, eh. In addition, he has even given him the key to the city.
corrupción y que tiene cierto buen Trato con Didi eh Además le ha dado hasta la llave de la ciudad
No, this lawyer has given an interview in which he has come out to clarify a little what happened
No pues este abogado ha dado una entrevista en la que ha salido a aclarar un poco lo sucedido
in that jaguar interview in the Pierce Morgan's program we were commenting on it in
en esa entrevista de jaguar en el programa de Pierce Morgan estuvimos comentándolo en
the two previous videos Jaguar accused JC and billion C of having super shady things including
los dos vídeos anteriores Jaguar acusó a JC y billon C de tener cosas super turbias incluidas
kidnappings and things like that and Pier Morgan upon receiving the notification from the lawyer
secuestros y cosas por el estilo y pier Morgan al recibir la notificación por parte del abogado
Well, he decided to notify so that the thing would not be more on the topic of bon c JC remaining silent
Pues decidió notificar para que la cosa no fuese más sobre el tema de que bon c JC se mantengan en
about all the accusations and everything that is happening with Didi because it does not clarify
silencio sobre todas las acusaciones y todo lo que está pasando con Didi pues no aclara
much simply that they will talk if they feel like talking at some point but practically that
mucho simplemente que hablarán si les apetece hablar en algún momento pero prácticamente que
what happened was a warning not only for Pier Morgan as such And for his program
lo de pier fue una advertencia no solamente para pier Morgan como tal Y para su programa
but for anyone who dares to accuse him of any crime or accuses the couple of whatever
sino para cualquiera que se atreva a imputarle algún delito o acusa al matrimonio de lo que
they have in mind as the accusation, according to the slander, they are going to defend themselves in
sea que tengan en cuenta de cuier acusación segú os calumnias se van a defender en los
court show and then of levels vish Were you ready for like this to eventually happen Listen
tribunales show and then of levels vish Were you ready for like this to eventually happen Listen
there's rumors and then there's nonsense and This is one Step further right This is a pointed and
there's rumors and then there's nonsense and This is one Step further right This is a pointed and
formal accusation of Something I felt it needed to be responded to so I think someone reported
formal accusation of Something I felt it needed to be responded to so I think somebody reported
It was a ceist it wasn't that It was quite bluntly an ultimatum which is remove that false accusation
It was a ceist it wasn't that It was quite bluntly an ultimatum which is remove that false accusation
um That's demonstrably false um or a court's Going To order you to and so I think he made
um That's demonstrably false um or a court's Going To order you to and so I think he made
the wise Choice and acted accordingly he meaning pier Morgan removing it and apologizing for it Yes
the wise Choice and acted accordingly he meaning pier Morgan removing it and apologizing for it Yes
What changed here in my mind is that someone On A so-called journalistic platform exploited that
What changed here in my mind is that somebody On A so-called journalistic platform exploited that
kind of Random ror mill whether It's disconnected from reality or What have you and lifted it up um
kind of Random ror mill whether It's disconnected from reality or What have you and lifted it up um
and by doing that you know they not only caused harm here but They are also drone out the voices
and by doing that you know they not only caused harm here but They are also droning out the voices
of real victims and by doing that to get clicks it didn't Just harm the Carters what what
of real victims and by doing that to get clicks it didn't Just harm the Carters what what what
he did effectively was to drone out the voices of of actual victims in an ongoing Case in an ongoing
he did effectively was to drone out the voices of of actual victims in an ongoing Case in an ongoing
investigation and that was that was too much for me what I am here to say is that in a situation
investigation and that was that was too much for me what I am here to say is that in a situation
as serious as this um someone Who puts them out as a journalist should not effectively Take
as serious as this um somebody Who puts them out as a journalist should not effectively Take
advantage of the situation and exploit someone in this way and so That's That's the real reason for
advantage of the situation and exploit somebody in this way and so That's That's the real Reason for
car I can Tell you that When they put their Foot down on something like they did here you
car I can Tell you that When they put their Foot down on something as they did here you
know They are sending a message and If they can't Stand up and and make sure right from wrong then
know They are sending a message and If they can't Stand up and and make sure right from wrong then
Who other than Apparently he has preferred to stay away from the subject. While the atmosphere is
Who otro que por lo visto ha preferido mantenerse alejado del tema Mientras que el ambiente está
hot, it has been Leonardo DiCaprio who is currently taking a vacation
calentito ha sido Leonardo DiCaprio que se encuentra ahora mismo tomarse unas vacaciones
with his girlfriend Victoria cti Italy who, by the way, recently turned 26, a new record for
con su novia Victoria cti Italia que por cierto recientemente cumplió 26 años nuevo récord para
Leonardo DiCaprio And he was leaving to all their partners every time they approached or reached
Leonardo DiCaprio Y es que estaba dejando a todas sus parejas cada vez que se acercaban o llegaban
the age of 25. So congratulations on the new record, you know that Leonardo DiCaprio has
a los 25 años Así que Enhorabuena por el nuevo récord ya sabéis que bueno Leonardo DiCaprio ha
been very involved in all the parties, he has attended Didi's parties a lot, he was very
estado muy involucrado en todas las fiestas ha asistido mucho a las fiestas de Didi estaba muy
present has done many things does not mean that he is guilty of anything but well the truth is that
presente ha hecho muchas cosas no significa que sea culpable de nada pero bueno la verdad es que
he has been seen a lot there at the moment he is not being investigated nor does he have any charges in
se le ha visto mucho por allí de momento no está siendo investigado ni tiene ninguna imputación en
the case but well yes serc is mentioning a lot about this case because there are a
el caso pero bueno sí que serc está mencionando mucho en torno a este caso porque es que salen un
lot of photos and a lot of videos appeared surrounded by all these people Mike Tyson of which I
montón de fotos y aparecion un montón de vídeos rodeado de toda esta gente Mike Tyson del que os
clicked on one of the last videos in which there was a slightly strange situation in
puse un click en uno de los últimos vídeos en el que había una situación un poco extraña en
a television program it didn't seem Like Didi wanted to touch his leg or something like that,
un programa de televisión no parecía como que Didi le quería tocar la pierna o algo por el
in an interview he gave to the Daily Mail, he made some statements when asked
estilo en una entrevista que ha dado al Daily mail ha hecho unas declaraciones cuando le han
about the subject that were considered somewhat unfortunate for the public. And he
preguntado sobre el tema que se han considerado un tanto desafortunadas para el público Y es que
said wait, I'm synonym of Didi Well that's great he said I never knew I wish him the best
ha dicho espera soy sinónimo de Didi Bueno eso es genial dijo nunca lo supe le deseo lo mejor
in life I wish him the best and it's clear that at this moment someone comes out who
en la vida le deseo lo mejor y es que claro en estos momentos que salga alguien que ya de por
is already confronting people who don't come out and talk. people are quiet and someone so
sí se está echando encara a la gente que no salga a hablar que la gente esté callada y salga uno tan
powerful and famous comes out wishing Didi luck because people have not taken it well the drummer of
potente tan famoso deseándole suerte a Didi pues la gente no se lo ha tomado bien el baterista de
blink 182 and his son lon had a party to celebrate the latter's 21 years parodying one
blink 182 y su hijo lon hicieron una fiesta para celebrar los 21 años de este último parodiando una
of the famous parties from Didi something that has not been taken well at all And it is that Who
de las famosas fiestas de Didi algo que no se ha tomado tampoco nada bien Y es que es que A quién
can think of at this moment not being famous and publish something similar But well I imagine that at
se le ocurre en estos momentos no siendo famoso y publicar Algo similar Pero bueno imagino que por
least we will always have humor left for me, for example I put this publication on Twitter a
lo menos siempre nos quedará el humor a mí por ejemplo puse esta publicación en Twitter hace un
couple of weeks ago and at a meeting of friends we had a party to celebrate an
par de semana y es que en una reunión de amigos que hicimos una fiesta para celebrar una fiesta
Ibizan party that they call it here we don't have to all dress in white and I made the joke
ibicenca que la llaman aquí no nos tenemos que vestir todos de blanco y puse la broma
about Didi's parties no and well yes, There was some comment that was made to me in responses
de las fiestas de Didi no y bueno sí que hubo algún comentario que me pusieron en respuestas
to the twit of people telling me Javi that's not a joke, patatín patatán and I understand that the atmosphere
al twit de gente diciéndome Javi eso no es para bromear patatín patatán y entiendo que el ambiente
is delicate and maybe it was an unfortunate joke and most of all, for his part, he starts
esté delicado y a lo mejor pues fue un chiste desafortunado y lo más por su parte comienza
talking about the elite and is warning of who wants to go out and also expose things, says that he
hablando de la élite está advirtiendo de que quiere salir y exponer también cositas dice que
probably knows 80% of the elite behind the media and that he knows how
probablemente conoce al 80% de la élite que está detrás de los medios y que conoce cómo
many puppets are handled. anyone kind of mastermind not like seems to be of mar
se manejan muchas marionetas anyone kind of mastermind not like seems to be of mar
some most
some most
has also mentioned the subject From Epstein's list, something that we were also discussing
también ha mencionado sobre el tema de la lista de epstein cosa que también estuvimos tratando
on the channel, you have a playlist or you can easily find it by going to the
en el canal tenéis una lista de reproducción o lo podéis encontrar fácilmente yendo a la página de
home page of my channel, there I have everything organized in series And yes, what he mentions is true
inicio de mi canal por ahí lo tengo todo ordenado en series Y sí que es verdad lo que menciona que
. Quite suspicious that such a shady case in which it has now been demonstrated, above all, the
es bastante sospechoso que un caso tan turbio en el que ahora se ha demostrado sobre todo las
serious things that were involved, that even though Epstein is not there, no one has been
cosas tan serias que había que a pesar de que epstein no esté no haya salido todavía Nadie
convicted yet, apart from his wife, for complicity and for being involved with that guy, he says. They are
condenado aparte de su mujer por complicidad y por estar involucrado con ese Tío dice que están muy
probably very busy investigating protesters but they never look at the powerful. It is curious
ocupado seguramente investigando manifestantes pero nunca miran a los poderosos que es curioso
that in one day they capture 600 protesters but that in a year no one from the epting lists allows me
que en un día capturen 600 manifestantes pero que en año a nadie de las listas de epting permitirme
but here I quite agree, curious at least not and the most pointed directly
pero aquí estoy bastante de acuerdo curioso cuanto menos no y los más apuntado directamente
to several millionaires, such as Reid Hoffman, creator of LinkedIn, Bill Gates, owner
a varios millonarios Como por ejemplo a reid Hoffman creador de linkedin a Bill Gates dueño
of Microsoft, whom we mentioned many times in this series we did about Jeffrey, and he claims
de Microsoft al que mencionamos muchas veces en la serie esta que hicimos sobre Jeffrey y afirma
that these two in particular would be especially terrified of what could come out of them
que estos dos en concreto estarían Especialmente aterrorizados con lo que pudiera salir de ellos
related to that island and be careful they would also be afraid if Trump won the elections well
relacionados con esa isla y ojo también estarían atemorizados si Trump ganara las elecciones bueno
See That list do you think I don't know It's It's Mind blowing that that um that they've
See That list do you think I don't know It's It's Mind blowing that that um that they've
not tried to prosecute even One not even the worst offender on on the F client list they've not even
not tried to prosecute even One not even the worst offender on on the F client list they've not even
tried to prosecute even One That's insane well Cuz they have a lot of diabetic grandmothers Who were
tried prosecute even One That's insane well Cuz they have a lot of diabetic grandmothers Who were
outside the capital on January 6 they they're kind of occupied yeah I mean they've put like Whatever
outside the capital on January 6 they they're kind of occupied yeah I mean they've put like Whatever
5 or 600 janary 6 protesters in Prison and not One person on the F client list Will That Ever come
5 or 600 janary 6 protesters in Prison and not One person on on the F client list Will That Ever come
out Do You Think You know II think part of Why kamal is getting so much Support is that Uh If If
out Do You Think You know I I think part of Why kamal is getting so much Support is that Uh If If
Trump wins that F client list is going to become public Yes and some of Those billionaires behind
Trump wins that F client list is going to become public Yes and some of Those billionaires behind
kamala are terrified of that outcome yeah do you think reed hoffman's uncomfortable Yes and Gates
kamala are terrified of that outcome yeah do you think reed hoffman's uncomfortable Yes and Gates
and Gates yeah And I only asked that Cuz You Can you just Look at them and You're like that That's
and Gates yeah And I only asked that Cuz You Can you just Look at them and You're like that That's
a nervous person right there I don't know I mean I assume you know them yeah Yes Uh reof was my
a nervous person right there I don't know I mean i assume you know them yeah Yes Uh reof was my
Vice President bu development of PayPal yeah 24 years ago he does he seem nervous to you yeah I
Vice President bu development of PayPal yeah 24 years ago he does he seem nervous to you yeah I
mean He's terrified of Trump victory Because of the disclosure That would follow I think yeah
mean He's terrified of Trump victory Because of the disclosure That would follow I think yeah
I mean I think He's certainly ideologically not aligned with Trump anyway but I think he
I mean I think He's certainly ideologically not aligned with Trump anyway but I think he
then affirms that between did epstein the government has to have hundreds of hours of recordings
luego afirma que entre did epstein el gobierno tiene que tener cientos de horas de grabaciones
found and wonders why they have not released it. He also says that the people in those
encontradas y se pregunta que por qué no la han sacado además dice que la gente en esos
videos who have not wanted to release the authorities are giving lectures and going from Adal to
vídeos que no han querido sacar a las autoridades están dando conferencias y yendo de Adal de la
morality surely in many parts of the country and the planet This is something that will surely
moral seguramente en muchas partes del país y del planeta Esto es algo que seguramente
seem quite common to you, it always does not fail to say that all these famous people and millionaires
os parecerá bastante habitual siempre no falla dice que todos estos famosos y millonarios les
like to question the morals of others a lot, taking advantage of the fact that they keep their
gusta cuestionar mucho la moral de los demás aprovechándose de que a ellos le guardan los
little secrets and I would also affirm that Thanks to Twitter, I'm not going to stop calling it Twitter.
secretitos y también afirmaría que gracias a x Twitter yo no voy a parar de llamarle Twitter
In life, all this is coming to light and is being talked about all over the world.
en la vida es que todo esto está saliendo a la luz y se está hablando en todo el mundo
of footage here Yeah yeah It's kind of weird that The People on Those videos are reading the Rest
of footage here Yeah yeah It's kind of weird that The People on Those videos are lecturing the Rest
of Us about Our moral failings isn't it yeah It's weird What is that um well I mean part of how they
of Us about Our moral failings isn't it yeah It's weird What is that um well I mean part of how they
deflect attention from themselves is by you know criticizing the morals of others Yes so they It's
deflect attention from themselves is by you know criticizing the morals of others Yes so they It's
sort of like a preemptive moral strike I mean as I said I think those who are saying Trump is a
sort of like a preemptive moral strike I mean as I said I think those who are saying Trump is a
threat to democracy are themselves actually the threat to democracy it feels like we're
threat to democracy are themselves actually the threat to democracy it feels like we're
Getting to a Place Where the Rest of Us know too much is this know what I mean It's easier
Getting to a Place Where the Rest of Us know too much is this know what I mean It's easier
than I really recommend that you look for that interview because he also says very
que por cierto recomiendo que busquéis esa entrevista porque dice cosas también muy
interesting things like that he is trying to create laws where people who
interesantes como que está creando intentando que se implanten leyes donde las personas que
do things on social networks pay for their crimes and take responsibility for the
hagan cosas en las redes sociales pues paguen por sus delitos no y se hagan cargo de las
things that are done on the internet but that of course on their platform they are going to fight because
cosas que se hacen en internet pero que por supuesto en su plataforma va a pelear porque
there is no censorship family here we are today's video I hope you liked it
no haya censura familia por aquí vamos estando el videito de hoy Espero que os haya gustado la
I really don't know if much more information will come out during the week this the truth is that it is non-
verdad no sé si durante la semana saldrá mucha más información esto la verdad es que es un no
stop I mean Honestly, it's a rare day when I don't wake up with a lot of new things and
parar o sea sinceramente es que raro es el día que no me despierto con un montón de cosas nuevas y
well, I owe it to you, I owe it to you because you want the information and you're going to have it here. So
bueno me debo a ustedes me debo a que queréis la información y aquí la Vais a tener Así que
if you want to continue having these videos on the channel, I recommend that you Subscribe, I activated the
si queréis seguir teniendo estos videítos por el canal os recomiendo que os suscribáis activé la
bell and above all, you always give me the like button because Although it may seem silly,
campanita y sobre todo que me regaláis siempre el botón de like porque Aunque parezca una tontería
this makes YouTube always put you there because it recommends all the videos I upload, okay,
Esto hace que YouTube siempre te te ponga por ahí por te recomiende todos los vídeos que subo vale
so don't stop by the channel to see the previous videos I send you a very strong kiss and
Así que nada pasaros por el canal para ver los vídeos anteriores os mando un beso muy fuerte y
until next time bye bye good weekend good weekend family also remind you that I have
hasta el próximo chao chao buen fin de semana buen fin de semana familia recordaros también que os he
left you videos in the salsería and on telesalseo in case you want to gossip a little more see you soon
dejado videítos en la salsería y en telesalseo por si queréis cotillear un poquito más hasta pronto